A Finding Aid to the National Arts Club Records, 1898-1960, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
Wild West party planned to benefit Jr. Members Scholarship Fund; to close 40th anniversary celebration. New York Times II, 2:8, April 23; New York Times II, 3:1, April 30.
Jr. Members plan New Year's Eve Olympian Ball. New York Times 30:2, December 19; New York Times II, 1:2, December 31.
1940
Art by deceased life members to be sold. New York Times 17:2, January 5.
Group show; awards. New York Times 21:2, January 11.
Group show. New York Times 24:2, January 24; New York Times IX, 9:2, January 28.
Non-members exhibition. Art News 38:15, February 3.
Exhibits: ceramics. New York Times 17:4, February 16; Ceramics and flowers. New York Times 15:5, February 19; Ceramics. New York Times II, 5:2, February 25; Exhibits: Jr. members. New York Times IX, 10:2, April 14; Group show awards. New York Times 21: 5, April 25.
Pan-American Ball held. New York Times 21:5, April 20.
Fund campaign for refugee artists started. New York Times 8:2, July 31.
Establishes artist refugee fund. New York Times 19:1, August 1.
Benefit exhibit plans. New York Times 20:8, October 2; Exhibit. New York Times IX, 5:4, October 6.
County fair planned. New York Times II, 3:3, October 6.
Refugee artists show their work. Art News 39:10, October 12.
Annual book exhibit opens. New York Times 3:5, November 3.
Testimonial luncheon for foreign authors in U.S. New York Times 45:2, November 10.
National Arts Club dramatizes books at the 35th annual new books of the year exhibition. Publishers Weekly 138:2046, November 30.
1941
Annual members' exhibit. New York Times 24:8, January 10; Comment. New York Times IX, 9:2, January 12; Awards. New York Times 24:6, January 23.
Annual prizes. Art Digest 15:13, February 1.
Benefits concerts planned. New York Times 39:1, February 23; New York Times 20:7, March 28.
Annual exhibit awards. New York Times 28:3, March 11; Comment. New York Times I, 10:3, March 16.
Group shows. New York Times IX, 10:1, March 30; New York Times IX, 8:2, May 25; New York Times X, 13:5, May 25; New York Times IX, 7:5, June 15.
Book exhibit. New York Times 1:6,November 9.
1942
Group show. New York Times X, 10:1, January 18.
Group show. New York Times 14:4, February 4; Private preview. New York Times 15:4, February 5; Comment. New York Times IX, 9:6, February 8.
Jr. members to honor servicemen at Hallowe'en party. New York Times 16:3, October 30.
37th annual show of new books. Publishers Weekly 142:2044, November 14.
To sponsor Chinese and Indian art exhibit in NYC. New York Times VIII, 9:1, December 13; Exhibit. New York Times 42:5, December 17.
1945
Holds Xmas fair. New York Times 13:3, November 16.
1946
Contemporary American painting exhibit planned. New York Times 23:6, February 20.
Jr. members and young non-members exhibition. Art News 45:67, May.
Annual book show plans. New York Times 21:2, November 1; Show, W.L. Laurence speaks. New York Times 13:1, November 12.
Annual book show. Publishers Weekly 150:2731, 2718, November 9.
Packaging the book. P. Boswell. Art Digest 21:3, November 15.
Choosing best book jackets, 41st annual book show. Art News 45:8, December.
1947
Preview exhibit. New York Times 21:5, January 9.
Forming symphony orchestra. New York Times 27:1, September 19.
1948
Ninth annual exhibition of American Veterans Society of Artists. Art Digest 22:19, January 1.
Conservatives score at the 50th annual exhibition of painting and sculpture. Art Digest 22:17, February 1.
Fiftieth annual exhibition. Art News 47:49, March.
Book fair opens in NYC. New York Times 30:7, December 9.
1949
Summer annual. Art Digest 23:14, August.
Dinner honors Mrs. F.D. Roosevelt. New York Times 39:5, October 11.
1950
Fifty-second annual exhibition of oils and sculptures. Art Digest 24:12, January 15.
Members' summer exhibition. Art Digest 24:18, August.
Fair plans. New York Times 44:8, November 1.
1951
Members-guests annual. New York Times II, 19:1, January 14.
53rd Annual Exhibition. Art Digest 25:18, January 15; Art News 49:47, February.
Non-members annual. New York Times 21:5, March 30.
Open competition for non-members. Art Digest 25:18, April 15.
Summer painting exhibition series opens. New York Times 42:8, June 7.
Members work. New York Times II, 6:4, June 17.
Summer exhibition. Art Digest 25:19, July.
1952
Fifty-fourth annual exhibition. Art Digest 26:19, January 15; Art News 49:47, February.
Members and guests annual. New York Times 59:2, January 6; Awards. New York Times 16:2, January 17.
Watercolor annual; awards. New York Times 14:4, February 8; Art News 51:56, March.
Non-members painting annual; awards. New York Times 16:5, March 10; New York Times 27:3, March 13.
Small pictures by members; awards. New York Times 25:5, April 9.
Exhibition of small oils. Art Digest 26:18-19, April 15; Art News 49:47, February.
1953
Theatre in an art gallery. A. Scheff. Theatre Arts 37:92, January.
Members-guests annual; awards. New York Times II, 11:2, January 11.
Non-members painting annual; awards. New York Times 21:5., February 19.
Members work; awards. New York Times II, 13:2, May 10; New York Times II, 8:5, June 21.
1954
Painting and sculpture annual by members and guests. New York Times 25:5, January 26.
Fifty-sixth annual exhibition. Arts Digest 28:17, February 1.
Members and non-members annual; contemporary watercolors; awards. New York Times 27:5, February 11; Review. New York Times II, 14:2, February 14.
Grand national annual members' competition. Art News 53:63, May.
1955
Painting and sculpture annual; awards. New York Times 23:1, January 12.
Fifty-sixth annual exhibition. Arts Digest 28:17, February 1.
Paintings annual; awards. New York Times 18:4, March 1.
Annual exhibition of American oil paintings. Art Digest 29:26, March 15.
Poet P. MacKaye honored on 80th birthday. New York Times 28:2, March 16.
1957
Arts Club honors Neuman; WNYC. C. Durgin. Musical America 77:12, April.
Art Clubs of America. Artist 53:67, June.
1958
At founding [sixtieth anniversary]. New York Times 49:2, November 27.
First annual metropolitan young artists show; awards. New York Times 49:2, November 27
1959
Stadium Concerts founder Mrs. C.S. Guggenheimer gets scroll from Mayor Wagner and National Arts Club medal. New York Times 9:2, March 12.
1960
Tenor competition awards. New York Times 47:8, November 15.
Provenance
The National Arts Club donated its records to the Archives of American Art in 1987. Although a limited amount of printed matter was available at various libraries and on microfilm through the Archives of American Art, scholars have not had access to unpublished records of the Club until this time.
In November 2017 an addition to the Officers' Correspondence was donated by Elizabeth G. Knudsen, granddaughter of Edmund Greacen, former Arts Committee Chair.
Restrictions on Access
The collection is open for research. Patrons must use microfilm copy.
Alternative Forms Available
The bulk of the collection is available on 35 mm microfilm reels 4237-4269 at the Archives of American Art offices and through interlibrary loan. Researchers should note that the arrangement of the material described in the container inventory does not reflect the arrangement of the collection on microfilm.
Appendix A: Annotated List of National Arts Club Exhibitions, 1899-1960
* = photographs included with records of NAC (See pp. 22-23 for reel and frame numbers)
+ = photograph in NAC album (See pp. 24 for reel and frame numbers)
x = catalog, checklist, or printed announcement included with NAC printed matter
s = copy of catalog in NAC scrapbook (volume number noted, see pp. 27-32 for reel and frame numbers of each volume)
Microfilm reel and frame numbers (e.g.: N134:416-419) are cited below for NAC catalogs appearing in other collections within the Archives of American Art.
Date Exhibition
Oct. 30 *, 1899 House Warming, Exhibition of American Gold and Silver Work
Nov. 13-18, 1899 Tenth Exhibition of the Woman's Art Club; Reception to Miss Cecilia Beaux (N134:416-419)
Nov. 27-Dec. 10, 1899 Art Pottery, American, Oriental, and European (N134:407-415)
Dec. 23-Jan. 8, 1899 Exhibition of Small Bronzes (N134:437-443)
Jan. 13, 1900 Exhibition of Photographs, works by members of the Society of Mural Painters
Jan. 29, 1900 Design for Street Refuge, shown by New York Municipal Art Society
Feb. 5-22, 1900 Exhibition of Embroideries and Native Rugs (N134:420-425)
Feb. 24-Mar. 10, 1900 John Leslie Breck Memorial Exhibition (N443:703-708; N551:719-724)
Mar. 24-Apr. 14, 1900 Pastel Exhibition, American Work
Apr., 1900 Old and Modern Japanese Prints
Apr. 14-21, 1900 Ernest Tarleton Memorial Exhibition
Apr. 21-May 3, 1900 Exhibition of Color Reproductions, American and European
May 10-21, 1900 American Art Leatherwork (N134:432-426)
May 24-30, 1900 Small Exhibition of Japanese Water Colors
May 31-June 14, 1900 William Hamilton Gibson Memorial Exhibition
June, 1900 New York Municipal Art Society Competition
Nov. 28-Dec. 19 x, 1900 Arts and Crafts (N134:421-431)
Jan., 1901 Birds and Beasts in Art
Feb., 1901 Art Leatherwork and Objects Relating to the Hearth
Mar., 1901 Works by the Society of Mural Painters
Apr., 1901 Books and Bookmaking
Apr., 1901 Howard Walter, Water Colors Taken in Europe
May, 1901 Glass in the Arts
May, 1901 Memorial to John A. Fraser, His Paintings
May-Nov., 1901 Arts and Crafts in the Liberal Arts Building, Pan-American Pacific Exhibition, Buffalo, N.Y.
June-Sept., 1901 Sculpture, Oil Paintings, Pastels, Water Colors, and Objects of Industrial Art by Members of the Club
Oct., 1901 Memorial Window for the Ames Family by John La Farge
Nov., 1901 Annual Exhibition of Paintings and Sculpture by the Woman's Art Club
Dec., 1901 Objects Shown at the Pan-American Pacific Exposition
Jan., 1902 Ecclesiastical Art
Feb., 1902 Art Objects Relating to Civic Art, under the auspices of the Municipal Art Society
Mar., 1902 American Pictorial Photographs, shown by the Photo-Secession
Mar. 26-Apr. 21, 1902 Fourth Annual Exhibition of the National Sculpture Society (N551:725-729; N134:446-451)
May, 1902 Pictures of "Womanhood"
May, 1902 Memorial Window for Baltimore by D. Maitland Armstrong; Memorial Window for Wells College by Mrs. Ella Condie Lamb June Window in Stained Glass, Memorial to Julia Doane, Chicago, by John La Farge
Oct., 1902 Collection of Objects in Metal; Artistic Bird Cages lent by A. W. Drake, Esq.
Nov., 1902 Annual Exhibition by the Woman's Art Club
Nov., 1902 Paintings by Four Western Artists, Messrs. Duveneck, Steele, Meakin and Sharp, through the courtesy of the Cincinnati Museum Association
Dec., 1902 Designs Submitted for Competition for the Emblem of the Louisiana Purchase Exposition
Jan. s, 1903 Portraits of Napoleon, lent by John Leonard Dudley, Jr., Esq. (volume 4)
Jan., 1903 "Autumn," Stained Glass Window for the country residence of William C. Whitney, by John La Farge
Feb., 1903 Eskimo and Arctic Objects, with Paintings from the Arctic and Antarctic Circles by Frank Wilbert Stokes
Mar., 1903 Objects of Municipal Art
Apr., 1903 Examples of Ideal Art by American Artists
May, 1903 Sculptures by Rodin, Roche, and Rivere, belonging to Miss Lois Fuller
May, 1903 Portraits and other Paintings by American Artists of the Colonial and Early Periods
June-Oct., 1903 Summer Exhibition of Paintings, Water Colors, and Sculpture by Members of the Club
Nov., 1903 Jewelry and Precious Stones, Modern, Old and Oriental
Dec. 1-14, 1903 Thirteenth Annual Exhibition of the Woman's Art Club (N134:452-456)
Dec., 1903 Stained Glass Window, designed by Miss Mary E. Tillinghast
Dec., 1903 Sketches for the Sculpture at the Louisiana Purchase Exposition, shown by the National Sculpture Society
Jan. 5-16 s, 1904 Loan Exhibition of Pictures by Eminent American Painters (N134:426-464, and volume 4)
Jan. 5-16 s, 1904 Loan Exhibition of Pictures by Robert Henri, William Glackens, George Luks, Arthur B. Davies, and Maurice Prendergast (volume 4)
Feb., 1904 Pictures by Contemporary American Artists
Mar. 2-15, 1904 Loan Exhibition of Pictures by American Figure Painters (N50:471-472; N134:460-461)
Mar., 1904 Annual Exhibition of Objects of Municipal Art
Apr. 5-15 s, 1904 Loan Exhibition of Pictures by Some Boston Artists (N443:713-715, and volume 4)
Apr. 19-30 s, 1904 Loan Exhibition of Pictures by Old Masters, lent by the Messrs. Durand-Ruel (N443:711-712; N134:462-464, and volume 4)
May 3-14 s, 1904 Oil Paintings, Water Colors, and Drawings by John La Farge, N.A. (volume 4)
May, 1904 Photographs of Paintings by Old Italian Masters, under the auspices of the Library Committee
Oct., 1904 Work of Holders of the Lazarus and Reinhart Scholarships executed while at the American Academy in Rome
Nov., 1904 "The Moral and Divine Law," painting by John La Farge
Nov., 1904 Exhibition by Members of the Nippon-Bijitsuin (Japanese Art Academy)
Jan., 1905 Exhibition by the Lyme Group of Painters
Feb., 1905 "Old Masters" and Aphrodite
Feb., 1905 Pictures by Some Boston Artists
Mar., 1905 Annual Exhibition of the Municipal Art Society of New York
Apr., 1905 Artistic and Commercial Posters, under the Auspices of the Municipal Art Society
Apr., 1905 Textiles and Ceramics
Oct., 1905 "Out of Doors" as Seen by Various Artists
Nov., 1905 Color Prints by S. Arlent-Edwards
Dec., 1905 American Indians as Seen by the Artist and the Artist Photographer
Jan., 1906 Birds and Beasts in Art
Feb., 1906 Miniatures
Mar., 1906 Fifth Annual Exhibition of the Municipal Art Society
Mar., 1906 Exhibition by the Alumni of Cooper Institute
Apr. 2-14 s, 1906 Municipal Art Society Exhibit of Poster Designs (volume 4)
Apr.-May, 1906 Exhibition by the Women's Art Club of New York
Nov. 8-18 s, 1906 Opening Exhibition [first exhibition in new quarters]: American Paintings from the Collection of Mr. William T. Evans (D45:29-34, and volume 4)
Dec., 1906 Books of the Year
Dec. 8-Jan. 1 s, 1906 Pictures by Some American Painters (volume 4)
Jan. 12-Feb. 1 s, 1907 Modern German Paintings from the Collection of Mr. Hugo Reisinger (N443:716-717, and volume 4)
Feb. s, 1907 Exhibition of Wood Engravings by Timothy Cole made for Century Magazine
Feb., 1907 Longfellow Memorial
Mar. 13-31, 1907 Sixth Annual Exhibition of the Municipal Art Society of New York
Apr., 1907 New York Society of Ceramic Artists
Apr., 1907 Paintings and Sculpture by Members
May s, 1907 Exhibition of Artists' Preliminary Sketches
May-Nov., 1907 Sketches by Members
Oct. 16-Nov. 16 s, 1907 Fall Exhibition of Sketches by Members (volume 4)
Nov. 20-Dec. 11, 1907 Arts and Crafts Exhibition (N29:1001-1026)
Dec., 1907 Second Annual Exhibition of the New Books of the Year
Jan. 4-25 s, 1908 Contemporary Art (N443:744-746, and volume 5)
Feb., 1908 First Annual Exhibition of Advertising Art
Feb. 1-15 s, 1908 Contemporary Paintings (volume 5)
Mar., 1908 Exhibition of the Municipal Art Society of New York
Apr. 2-25 * s, 1908 Special Exhibition of Members' Work (volume 5)
Apr. 15-May 8 s, 1908 Members' Spring Exhibition (volume 5)
Apr. 25-May 15 s, 1908 Paintings Loaned by C. C. Ruthrauff (volume 5)
May *, 1908 Exhibition of Painting, Sculpture, and Illustration under the auspices of the Art Students League of New York
Oct. 21-Nov. 7 s, 1908 Members' Fall Sketch Exhibition (volume 5)
Nov. *, 1908 Third Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
Dec., 1908 Arts and Crafts Exhibition
Jan., 1909 Second Annual Exhibition of Advertising Art
Jan., 1909 Small Exhibition of Paintings and Drawings by Contemporary Artists
Feb. 2-20 s, 1909 International Exhibition of Pictorial Photography (volume 1)
Feb. 23-Mar. 17 s, 1909 John W. Alexander Retrospective Exhibition (volume 5)
Apr., 1909 Exhibition of the New York Society of Keramic Arts
May, 1909 Spring Exhibition of Members' Work
July, 1909 Paintings from the Collection of Mr. and Mrs. William T. Evans
Sept.-Oct., 1909 Three Centuries of New York, under the auspices of the Hudson-Fulton Celebration
Nov. 3-26 s, 1909 Fourth Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year (volume 5)
Dec., 1909 Third Annual Exhibition of Arts and Crafts
Jan., 1910 William M. Chase Retrospective Exhibition
Feb., 1910 Exhibition of American Landscape Painting
Mar. 2-28 s, 1910 Exhibition of Paintings by Louis Mark, of Budapest (volume 5)
Apr. 6-30 s, 1910 Exhibition of Paintings by Alfred East, of London (N134:465-469, and volume 5)
May, 1910 Exhibition of Household Art, under the auspices of the Domestic Training Department of the Public Schools
May 4-Oct. s, 1910 Third Annual Exhibition of the Former Students of the Art Students League (volume 5)
Oct. 20-Nov. 1 s +, 1910 Third Annual Exhibition of Advertising Art (volume 5)
Nov.-Dec., 1910 Fifth Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
Dec. * +, 1910 Fourth Annual Arts and Crafts Exhibition
Jan. 5-Feb. 3 s +, 1911 First Annual Artist Life Members' Exhibition (volume 5)
Feb. +, 1911 Exhibition of the New York Society of Keramic Arts
Feb. 11-Mar. 10, 1911 Circuit Exhibition of Contemporary Art (D12:437-439; N52:105-107)
Mar. 8-Apr. 5 * s +, 1911 Paintings and Drawings by Walter Shirlaw, N.A. (N52:967-973, and volume 5)
Apr., 1911 Exhibition of the Municipal Art Society of New York
Apr. 26-May * s +, 1911 Group Exhibition of Paintings: William R. Derrick, Reynolds Beal, Frederick J. Waugh (volume 5)
Oct. 25-Nov. 4 * +, 1911 Exhibition of Color Schemes and Model Rooms in Miniature
Nov. 8-30 * +, 1911 Sixth Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
Dec. 7-28 * +, 1911 Fifth Annual Arts and Crafts Exhibition
Jan. 3-28 s +, 1912 First Prize Exhibition of Artist Life Members (N443:754-756, and volume 6)
Jan. 31-Feb. 18 * s +, 1912 Otto Walter Beck Exhibition (volume 6)
Feb. 21-Mar. 10 s +, 1912 Etchings of E. T. Hurley (volume 6)
Mar. 13-20 s +, 1912 National Park Pictures Collected and Exhibited by the Department of the Interior (volume 3)
Apr. 4-21 s +, 1912 Paintings, Embroideries, and Tapestries from the Collection of Mr. Emerson McMillan (D45:462-468; N443:757-762, and volume 6)
Apr. 4-Mar. 12 s, 1912 Exhibition of Original Dickens and Thackeray Drawings by Harry Furniss (volume 3)
May 8-June 1 * s +, 1912 Sculpture Exhibition (volume 6)
June 4-8 +, 1912 Exhibition of Industrial Art, under the auspices of The School Art League and the Art Departments of the City High Schools
June-Oct., 1912 Summer Exhibition of Painting and Sculpture
Oct. 16-Nov. 12 +, 1912 Third Special Exhibition of the Society of Illustrators
Nov. 13-29, 1912 Seventh Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
Dec. 4-28 +, 1912 Sixth Annual Exhibition of the National Society of Craftsmen
Jan. 8-Feb. 9 +, 1913 Work of the Painter, Sculptor, and Architect Members (N443:763-767; N50:126-130)
Feb. 12-Mar. 9 * +, 1913 Exhibition of Works by the Late Frederick Warren Freer
Mar. 12-31 +, 1913 The Applied Arts of Germany
Apr. 2-27 +, 1913 Small Works by Six Painters: Richard E. Miller, Frederick Carl Frieseke, Charles W. Hawthorne, William Wendt, William Ritschel, and Elise Dodge Pattee
Apr. 30-June 1 +, 1913 Small Marbles and Bronzes (N551:732-737)
May-June, 1913 Summer Exhibition of Paintings and Sculpture
Oct. 15-Nov. 9, 1913 Society of Illustrators
Nov. 12-28, 1913 Eighth Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
Dec. 3-28 * +, 1913 Seventh Annual Exhibition of the National Society of Craftsmen
Jan. 8-Feb. 1 +, 1914 Work of Painter, Sculptor, and Architect Members
Feb. 4-21, 1914 The Pastellists
Feb. 5-Mar. 21 x +, 1914 Contemporary Art
Mar. 11-29 * +, 1914 Hungarian Peasant Art (N134:470-479)
Apr. 1-May 2 +, 1914 Paintings by Eleven Western Artists
May 6-31 * +, 1914 Exhibition of Small Sculpture (N551:738-743)
June-Sept., 1914 Paintings
Nov. 4-27, 1914 Ninth Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
Dec. 3-28 +, 1914 Eighth Annual Exhibition of National Society of Craftsmen
Jan. 7-31 +, 1915 Work of Painter Members (N551:744-746)
Feb. 4-25 +, 1915 Forty-eighth Annual Exhibition of American Water Color Society
Mar. 3-24 +, 1915 Portraits (N551:747-748)
Apr. 7-13 +, 1915 Sculpture
May 5-21, 1915 Exhibition of Municipal Art Society
June-Oct. *, 1915 Work of Painter Members
Oct. 13-30 +, 1915 Fifth Special Exhibition of the Society of Illustrators
Nov. 5-13 +, 1915 American Wood Engraving, under the auspices of the American Institute of Graphic Arts
Nov. 17-Dec. 3, 1915 Tenth Anniversary Exhibition of Books of the Year
Dec. 8-30 +, 1915 Ninth Annual Exhibition of the National Society of Craftsmen
Jan. 6-28 +, 1916 Work of Painter Members
Feb. 3-27 +, 1916 Forty-ninth Annual Exhibition of American Water Color Society
Mar. 2-25 * +, 1916 Loan Exhibition of Portraits of Academicians and Associates Selected from the Permanent Collection of the National Academy of Design (N551:749-752; N134:480-483)
Mar. 28-Apr. 14 +, 1916 One Hundred American Paintings by the American Institute of Graphic Arts (N443:768-770)
Mar. 28-Apr. 14 +, 1916 Exhibition of American Printing
Apr. 19-May 6, 1916 Exhibition of the Municipal Art Society
May 10-26, 1916 English Posters
June-Aug. +, 1916 Members' Summer Sketch Exhibition
Oct. 5-Nov. 3, 1916 Photography, under the auspices of the American Institute of Graphic Arts
Nov. 9-30, 1916 Eleventh Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
Dec. 7-29, 1916 Tenth Annual Exhibition of the National Society of Craftsmen
Jan. 3-28 +, 1917 Annual Exhibition of the Work of Artist Members
Feb. 1-24 +, 1917 Fiftieth Annual Exhibition of the American Water Color Society
Feb. 28-Mar. 23 +, 1917 Etchings, under the auspices of the American Institute of Graphic Arts
Mar. 29-Apr. 27, 1917 Paintings by Boston Artists
May 2-Sept. +, 1917 Members' Sketch Exhibition
Oct. 3-31 +, 1917 Paintings from the Netherlands Section of the Panama-Pacific Exposition
Oct. 4-31, 1917 Illustrations of the Catskill Aqueduct
Nov. 8-30 +, 1917 Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
Dec. 6-29, 1917 Eleventh Annual Exhibition of the National Society of Craftsmen
Jan. 3-Feb. 1 +, 1918 Annual Exhibition of Paintings by Members
Feb. 7-Mar. 1 +, 1918 Fifty-first Annual Exhibition of the American Water Color Society
Mar. 20-Apr. 26, 1918 Life Membership Pictures from the Permanent Collection
May, 1918 War Posters, under the auspices of the American Society of Graphic Arts
June 2-Oct. 1 +, 1918 Sketch Exhibition by Members
Dec. 5-28 +, 1918 Twelfth Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
Jan. 8-31 +, 1919 Retrospective Exhibition of the Work of the Artist Life Members
Feb., 1919 Fifty-second Annual Exhibition of the American Water Color Society
Mar., 1919 Exhibition of War Housing
Apr. 2-May 3 +, 1919 Special Exhibition of the Society of Illustrators (N29:873-875)
May-Oct. +, 1919 Annual Exhibition of Sketches by Members
Nov., 1919 Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
Jan. 7-30 +, 1920 Annual Exhibition of Painter and Sculptor Members (N29:864-866)
Feb., 1920 Fifty-third Annual Exhibition of the American Water Color Society
Mar., 1920 Drawings from Artists' Portfolios
Mar. 3-27 x +, 1920 American Drawings and Sculpture Sketches
Mar. 31-Apr. 16 +, 1920 Special Exhibition of the Society of Illustrators (N29:867-869)
May, 1920 Printing by the American Institute of Graphic Arts
June-Oct. +, 1920 Sketches and Small Sculpture by Members
Nov., 1920 Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
Dec. 1-29 +, 1920 Exhibition of Art Expression by Club Members
Jan. 5-27 +, 1921 Members' Annual Prize Exhibition
Mar. 2-31 +, 1921 Art Directors Club First Annual Exhibition of Drawings and Paintings Used in American Advertising
Apr. 7-30, 1921 Exhibition of Old Prints, under the auspices of the American Institute of Graphic Arts (N443:775-778)
May-Oct., 1921 Pictures from the Club's Permanent Collection
Nov., 1921 Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
Dec. 7-30 +, 1921 Humorists Exhibition
Jan. 5-28 +, 1922 Members' Annual Prize Exhibition
Feb., 1922 Seventh Annual Exhibition of Contemporary Bookplates, held by the American Bookplate Society
Feb. 15-Mar. 5 +, 1922 Exhibition of Paintings by Charles C.Curran, Franklin de Haven, George Glenn Newell, Harry W. Watrous